Lukin Maksim, Software Engineer, http://lukin.io

Feb 19, 1990, Eastern Europe, Married

Experience:

— Ruby on Rails developer at <u>Lukin.io</u> (2019 – 2020, 1y)

Helping business and companies to grow by consulting, developing and supporting using Software Engineering practices, designing API.

— Ruby on Rails developer at Aejis (2018 – 2019, 1y)

Ruby (and Rails), sometimes NodeJS/React for outsourcing company, designing API.

— Ruby/JS Engineer, Team Lead/PM at <u>Facewatch</u> (2013 – 2018, *5y*)

Backend development using Ruby and Sinatra. Small services based on Ruby on Rails. API based on service oriented architecture, Amazon services. Frontend based on BackboneJS. Integration with Metropolitan Police (London), Facial recognition using external API. Security Audit/PenTests. Writing RSpec tests and documentation. Implement new API.

— iOS Engineer at <u>jaccomo</u>, <u>EVENTAGRATE</u> (2012 – 2013, **1y**)

Developing corporate applications for iPad, bluetooth messenger for conferences. Porting from Java/Swing application to iOS application. Development of jPass application.

— Ruby on Rails developer at GAP Intelligence (2009 – 2011, 2y)

Backend/Frontend development of DataCenter v2. DevOps tasks.

Interests:

Interested in Python, GO, TypeScript, Hardware (IoT), learning new technologies, self-development.

Summary:

Writing clean, $\underline{\text{SOLID}}$ code. Tests, automated tests, CI/CD, Amazon services.

Experience in development with Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, API, Redis, Sidekiq

Understanding Frontend-related side, HTML/CSS, JS (TypeScript, ReactJS, Redux, Backbone.js);

DevOps basic skills (Linux, Chef/Ansible, Docker);

Had experience in iOS development, NodeJS;

Agile/Scrum, TDD/BDD;

Education:

Hardware Engineering faculty (Professional College of Computer Science, 2003-2006);

Contacts:

Mobile: +38 (063) 765-49-17 Email: lukin.maksim@gmail.com

Skype: lukin.maksim

Github: https://github.com/sesharim **Linkedin**: https://linkedin.com/in/sesharim